<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jodi Lewis, Soprano</title>
    <link>https://jodi-lewis.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jodi Lewis, Soprano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:30:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jodi-lewis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>https://jodi-lewis.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jodi-lewis.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Jodi Lewis&amp;rsquo;s love for Opera began when she sang in her first opera scene at the age of 14. She knew then that singing was what she wanted to do for the rest of her life. Her passion drove her to the University of Illinois where she received a Bachelors of Music in Vocal Performance. While at Illinois, Jodi had the opportunity to perform small roles in operas, such as Dialogues of the Carmelites, La Périchole, and Suor Angelica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jodi-lewis.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jodi-lewis.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>To contact Jodi for voice lessons: studio@jodi-lewis.com
To contact Jodi for possible performances: performances@jodi-lewis.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance</title>
      <link>https://jodi-lewis.com/performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jodi-lewis.com/performance/</guid>
      <description>Full Roles    Donna Anna, in Don Giovanni, by W.A. Mozart Triangle Opera Studio, Raleigh, NC, 2009   Dido, in Dido and Æneas, by H.Purcell Pennsylvania State University, 2002   Jenny, in Three Sisters, Who are Not Sisters, by N. Rorem Pennsylvania State University, 2001   Alida Slade, in Roman Fever, by P. Hagemann Pennsylvania State University, 2001   Berginella, in La Périchole, by J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio</title>
      <link>https://jodi-lewis.com/studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jodi-lewis.com/studio/</guid>
      <description>Jodi Lewis has a Masters degree in Vocal Performance/Pedagogy from the Pennsylvania State University and a Bachelors in Vocal Performance from the University of Illinois. Jodi has been teaching voice and performing for over fifteen years. She is passionate about sharing her knowledge with others to enhance their sense of security and pride in their voices. She is currently accepting voice students of all levels, ages and abilities.
Jodi does not teach one particular style of music, but rather helps the students develop the foundation and technique that will enable them to sing any style they choose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>